https://www.autoracing1.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for AutoRacing1.com  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.  It will notify you of the following:
1.  What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2.  What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3.  The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4.  How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to respond to an email request from you.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
We may change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions through this website. This policy has been revised as of August 2020.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
–      See what data we have about you, if any.
–      Change/correct any data we have about you.
–      Have us delete any data we have about you.
–      Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to PayPal securely.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Privacy Questions
If you have any questions or concerns about the AutoRacing1.com Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us.
AutoRacing1.com may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately contact us.
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Editorials
Hot News
Main Categories
Automotive
Drag Racing
IHRA
December 10, 2020
CEO Louis Camilleri retires from Ferrari, or was he ousted?
(Update)
December 10, 2020
Hamilton back for Abu Dhabi
December 10, 2020
F2: Delétraz tops final day of post-season testing in Sakhir
December 10, 2020
Russians defend Mazepin amid ‘groping’ scandal
(Update)
December 10, 2020
Mike Bumgarner Named Crew Chief for JRM’s No. 1 Team
December 10, 2020
RCR and TaxSlayer Extend Partnership in 2021 with Myatt Snider
December 10, 2020
Team Netherlands will race in Rolex 24
December 10, 2020
Magnus with Archangel Puts Lally, Potter Behind Wheel of Acura NSX
December 10, 2020
IMSA teams carry out pre-season testing at Daytona
December 10, 2020
Johnson, Pagenaud, Kobayashi, and Rockenfeller to run Rolex 24 w/Action Express
(Update)
December 10, 2020
Marko plays down Perez, Russell rumors
December 10, 2020
Wolff ‘curious’ to see Ocon’s next steps in F1
December 10, 2020
No ‘young driver’ test for Sainz or Vettel
December 10, 2020
Nashville Superspeedway rebrands ahead of Cup race in June
January 2001
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
